applegamer.com 2013-05-04

# Privacy Policy - applegamer.com

## Privacy Policy 

### Imprint

Christian Vorbeck  
Bruno-Apitz-Str. 10  
13125 Berlin  
Germany 

Phone/Telefon: +49 (30)947 963 67  
Email: trixta at gmx dot net  

### General Privacy Information

This site contains links to affiliates, clients, vendors, sponsors, advertisers and other third party internet sites and services who may collect data in connection with sweepstakes, promotions, surveys, e-commerce, etc. They each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of this site and AppleGamer has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such sites. Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily and publicly disclose personal information on any online service or website - for example through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. Further, while AppleGamer takes reasonable steps to protect your personal information using the security and other measures set forth herein, AppleGamer cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us, and you do so at your own risk. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. 

### Collection and Use of Information

This site collects information about you both from what you tell AppleGamer and what AppleGamer collects through the use of cookies (see Cookies below). Information collected about you is used in two different ways. Information is "aggregated" -- meaning that the information from many users is grouped together in a way that does not disclose the personal information of any particular user. AppleGamer may use this aggregated information to determine user traffic statistics for this site (including without limitation to determine browser usage, duration of stay, the referring URL, IP address geographical location, etc.) and to evaluate which games and services are successful and which ones are not, and in order to evaluate which new services or games hat we should make available on this site. AppleGamer may use only the anonymous click stream data to help our advertisers and sponsors deliver better-targeted advertisements. In addition, some of your personal information may be shared with third parties who assist AppleGamer in producing, maintaining, servicing, and running this site or provide a service to this site's users. 

### Registration

Anyone who participates in any interactive activities offered (or to be offered in the future) on this site may be asked to register for a free ID and password or to complete subscription registration for an ID and password. AppleGamer use this contact information from this registration form to send the registrant information about AppleGamer, AppleGamers events and new services or game productions. Users may always opt-out of receiving any such information either by responding to the relevant communication as directed or by contacting this site (see Contacting This Site and Changing Your Personal Information below). 

### Child Online Protection Act Notification

Pursuant to 47 U.S.C. Section 230(d) as amended, AppleGamer hereby notifies you that parental control provisions (such as computer hardware, software, or filtering services) are commercially available that may assist you in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors. Information identifying current providers of such protections is available at the Electronic Frontier Foundation Website, http://www.eff.org/pub/Censorship/Ratings_filters_labelling/, and at the American Links Up Website, http://www.netparents.org/parentstips/browsers.html. To view information on our policy regarding the privacy of children under the age of 13, please see AppleGamers Privacy Policy below. 

### Children Under the Age of 13

This Privacy Policy describes AppleGamers practices of collecting, using and disclosing any personal information collected by AppleGamers from all visitors to this site, therefore including visitors who are children under the age of 13. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, you may contact AppleGamers by email at trixta at gmx dot net. 

AppleGamer collects personal information from those who access this site. No user is required to disclose more information than is reasonably necessary. Any collected information is for AppleGamers internal purposes only, and is not disclosed to third parties. Information may be used for marketing purposes, and/or to provide you with AppleGamer information that AppleGamer believes may be of interest to the user. In order to receive such information, marketing and otherwise, it is necessary for you to establish an account with AppleGamer. 

It is AppleGamers intent to adhere to the provisions of the Children's Online Protection and Privacy Act of 1998 (U.S.C. 6501 et seq.) ("COPPA"). No child who visits this site is required to provide any information in order to access most of this site. If you are under age 13, please have a parent or guardian establish your account on this site. For account registration on this site, AppleGamer requires your name and email address. AppleGamer will not contact children under age 13 regarding special offers or for marketing purpose without parental/guardian consent. A parent or guardian may review his or her child's personal information, ask to have it deleted and/or refuse to allow any further collection or use of his or her child's information from this site. To do any of the foregoing, please contact this site's operator through one of the methods listed above. 

### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that certain websites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain your user information. But the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. AppleGamer uses cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to optimize AppleGamers services. Users should be aware that this site cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information placed by advertisers or third parties hosting data for this site. 

### Security

This site utilizes a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. All user contact information is contained behind a "firewall" and only accessible by a limited number of employees who have special access rights to production systems. 

### Agreement

By using applegamer.com, you agree to the applegamer.com Online Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to this Privacy Policy, please do not use this site. You agree that AppleGamer may change this Privacy Policy and the main AppleGamer Terms and Conditions at any time. Please check our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions from time to time to ensure that you are aware of any changes. You can find our current Privacy Policy here: http://applegamer.com/privacy-policy. Your continued use of this site will signify your acceptance of any changes in our Privacy Policy. 

### Third party

**Valueclick Media**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here (<http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>). 

**Other Third Party**  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies. For additional informations please visit auf partner sites.   
See: [Google](http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html)  
See: [MochiMedia](http://www.mochimedia.com/privacy.html)  
See: [CPMStar](http://www.cpmstar.com/index.aspx?nav=privacy) and [Third Party](http://www.cpmstar.com/index.aspx?nav=thirdpartyprivacy)  
See: [AdToll](http://www.adtoll.com/privacy_statement)  
See: [Kitara Media](http://kitaramedia.com/privacy_kitara.html)

### Additional Information

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.
